*Your info
	-ID: 1412280
	-Name: Trần Hoàng Lâm
	-Email: malartsoft@gmail.com

*What you have done
	-Write a program to periodically every 2 second save a picture of the screen to disk. 
	Activate with Ctrl + Alt + Shift + S.Filename should be in this format: "Screen yymmdd hhmmss.bmp"
	
	-Write a program to log all clipboard activity into files.
	Activate with Ctrl + Alt + Shift + C.

*Link youtube guide: https://youtu.be/dAUxZaNIGr4

*Link github: https://github.com/malartsoft/GuessFlag

**********************************App Screen watch***************************************************************
*Main flow
	1. Open app
	2. Press the key combination Ctrl + Alt + Shift + S to start, program will run hide
	3. After each 2s, program will write screen image on file, with format name file "Screen yymmdd hhmmss.bmp"
   	   All file image save in folder "Image_ScreenWatch"
	4. Press the key combination Ctrl + Alt + Shift + S again to end, program will appear become
	5. Click 'X' to exit

*Additional flow
	5.1 Choose File -> exit to exit

**********************************App Trash Hijack***************************************************************
*Main flow
	1. Open app Trash Hijack
	2. Press the key combination Ctrl + Alt + Shift + C to start, program will run hide
	3. Exemple copy text. After each 2s, program will write this text into file
   	   with file name is Text_Clipboard
	4. Exemple press PrntScr. After each 2s, program will write this image screen 
           on file with format name file "Screen yymmdd hhmmss.bmp". 
           All file image save in folder "Image_Screen_Clipboard"
	5. Press the key combination Ctrl + Alt + Shift + C again to end
	   Program will appear become
	6. Click 'X' to exit

*Additional flow
	5.1 Choose File -> exit to exit
